Hello Hello Friends
that ICICI Pru target should be
kept for 10 minutes from 25th October onwards, let's study
this, please pay attention, in ICICI Pru,
like share was first pulling upwards,
it came down from the top, it has
started changing by making a downward movement, I am
showing you the chart, see this,
when it came downwards, it reached the support at the lower hair pack,
see it went up and then it has come to the same level,
sure it was done on a pass earlier, so support can be found from here at
the moment, you will get support,
click, your first target should be 6,
you will see 55th, which will be visible at the moment, so
friends, keep all this in mind